After graduating from high school,
Leone Abbacchio immediately
followed his deep sense
of justice directly into a
job with the police force.
But the realization of his
dream did little to quell the
unease he felt from the contradictions
plaguing his daily work.
The people he was expected to
defend each day were the very ones
causing trouble around the city he
risked his life to serve and protect.
These ne 'er-do-wells seemed to revel
in destroying law enforcement property,
stealing from the public, and committing
other heinous acts of depravity.
It was a thankless job, and the demands
never seemed to stop, nor did the insults or
verbal humiliations.
He imperiled his life again and again
to put the dregs of society behind bars,
But this was a city where money talked,
and criminals, more often than not, walked.
Quit stirring up trouble. Sorry.
It don't matter now.
The contradictions became one
of Abakio's greatest teachers.
Ah, come on, officer.
Cut us some slack.
What do you say?
You wouldn't arrest a lady whose
daddy was in debt, would you?
She needs the cash real bad.
We're just minding our own business.
Would you hurry it up?
I got a good customer over here.
I'm working on it!
Even if I do arrest these bastards,
I'll just post bail and walk away.
They'll either try to pay me off,
or they'll just throw cash
at the courts and lawyers.
You're a real man of passion, aren't you?
The kind of cop who
takes his job seriously.
Then, one night, reports came
in detailing a nearby robbery.
Police! Freeze!
Well, hey, it's been a while.
Guess I...
You again screwed the pooch this time.
Someone blew his brains out.
You can just pretend you
never saw this, right?
Come on, it'll be our little secret.
I'll never bother you again.
Not a chance.
You're finished.
Hey, let's not be too hasty.
If you arrest me, what incentive would
I have to keep quiet about that bribe?
One more thing.
You shouldn't play with guns.
Mind pointing that thing somewhere else?
Move, Abakyo! He's got a gun!
It was this moment that would mark
the beginning of the end for Abakio.
He was labeled a dirty cop
and punished accordingly.
What was worse,
he'd lost his partner
because of his own actions,
a truth he would have to forever endure.
The compounding disasters sent him
spiraling into a deep depression.
Live, die, or suffer,
it seemed nothing would ever free him from
the grief that had entangled his heart.
Abokyo.
Pleasure's mine.
Thank you.
FIGHTING GOLD
Go on.
Solve it then.
Don't let me down. Giorno!
Have you lost your mind?
No! Giorno!
Giorno's in trouble.
Giorno Giovanna.
You're one foley Radio.
To go to these lengths to prove yourself.
This kid's even crazier than I thought!
Maledetto!
What's going on with this stand? Quick!
Use Golden Wings!
Impossible!
Giorno, where are you?
It's best you remain up here, Bucciarati.
Better yet, stay back.
Try not to misunderstand.
I still don't consider Giorno one of us.
But given his words, he thinks that
you're going to come to his rescue,
as well as our comrades.
Honestly, this guy's a total whack job.
What the hell were you thinking?
Those juvenile theatrics could
have gotten your dumbass kill.
Listen, Pucerati.
You have to remain up here.
Wait.
Isn't that fly?
Narancia's shoe?
Giorno's powers are still active.
He could still be alive.
The others are here.
Narancia and that bastard are down there.
Superman!
Narancia, Fugo, Mista,
and Giorno are gone.
Could they be right under the fly?
It's just like Giorno said.
The enemy isn't hiding
in some locker or shadow.
There's something else going on here.
Look, the flies coming this way.
Bizarre.
Just where is it going now?
How are they hiding like this?
Where could they be?
I've Never seen anything
like these powers.
I can't believe it.
That show off.
Actually Managed to get something right.
I'm gonna expose this bastard.
But first we have to
Get away from this spot.
Moody Jazz! Let's jam!
Let's try Narancia, five minutes ago.
That should be more than enough.
What about that fly?
It's heading toward the bow.
We don't have much time. Work fast. Right.
What's that noise?
His headphones.
About five minutes ago,
Narancia was listening to music.
What the?
Why the hell did it just stop playing?
No, this isn't it.
Whatever attack Narancia
did so after this.
I'll fast-forward a bit.
That lira belongs to us now!
With capital like that,
we'll claim the rank of Cape!
Oh, hell yeah!
I heard my voice just now.
It was right after this
that Narancia was taking it.
This had better show us exactly
how he was attacked, Abakio.
Well, my stand can replay
anything it records.
We can observe everything from his
heart rate to his perspiration.
And it'll follow him wherever he goes.
The time's come.
Get behind Naranta and watch
for when he's grabbed him.
There! Look!
Giorno had that same gas!
No!
What?
It's like watching a deflating balloon.
He's withering away!
His wound is releasing
air, deflating his body.
Looks like we got the scoop
on this Katsune's abilities.
Something's pulling him in!
Habakio! Pause it now!
I see.
He's inside the pipe.
We might find the answer here.
Everything from his nails to his bones is
rubbery like some kind of weird condom.
Even his shoe and buckle are rubber.
Good news is, I still feel a pulse.
It's as Giorno said, he's alive.
That explains it then.
Our enemy is also rubber.
He's shifty, hiding between
pipes, planks, and walls.
That's how he managed to
capture Mista, Fugo, and Giorno.
And why the fly got a small blip,
but despite its best efforts,
couldn't completely hone in
on the enemy's exact location.
Looks like we exposed the enemy's secret.
Now we track down that rotten rubber.
Once we do that, we rescue
Narancia and the others.
Then we deliver one hell of a beatdown.
But first, get ready for more moody jazz!
Track it down?
Have you lost it?
You can't attack or defend during replay.
It's too risky.
You're asking for it if you go in there.
I know the precise movement and
location of Moody Jazz at all times.
When the bastard gets close, you unzip the
floor and beat his ass to Kingdom Come.
We won't defeat him by sitting
here, twiddling our thumbs.
Let's attack.
It went left.
That's where he got Miska.
Moody Jazz is passing
underneath the buoy as we speak.
Now it's taking a detour to the
cabin where it got Fugo and Giorno.
So the enemy can hold them captive
and move them exactly where he wants.
Look, the fly's beginning to slow down.
That's the same spot he was hiding before.
Yes, on the inside of that rope tie.
He's directly below the deck.
Seems he's heading our way.
He might know we found out
the secret behind his attack.
He's got balls.
Now's our chance.
Cut the pipes and pull them out.
Zipper Man!
They're nowhere to be found.
Where's our target now, Abakio?
Where's Moody Jazz?
Where are the others?
Right there.
There's no doubt my stand
is still in front of us.
It's right over there.
But I don't see a damn thing.
It's right where you opened the zipper.
Just trust me on this.
I know where my stand is.
Where are they? Good question.
There's no way he vanished.
He's right there.
Is there another mystery
we haven't figured out?
Something's wrong.
Stop the replay and recall your stand.
I already did.
Something's wrong.
I'm not recognizing this wall.
Which crack did you crawl into now?
Hear that hollow thud?
That sound was the pipe wall.
Look, I know you can't see him, but
Moody Jazz is currently under our noses.
Inside the pipe.
What are you doing?
The pipe's wide open.
The enemy's right in front of us.
There's nothing there.
He's hiding under us somehow.
We gotta go.
You wanna run?
Damn that grating do-gooder
Giorno Ordering me to
solve this mystery Impudent
punk He's lucky I'm nice Bakio
It's coming
There's one more mystery And I've
just about cracked it Once I do,
I'll crack his skull There was something
about that mast Something wrong
The enemy's here!
Withdraw your stand! I got it!
I just blew this whole mystery wide open!
Fuck you!
Now the coup de Crazy, Poutarati!
That's a neat trick!
And an impressive hideout!
He's gone, you two!
Grab onto me!
Damn it!
He's gone!
Where'd he go?
What?
What did you do with the
He's not in the cabin
And he's not in the pipe
Where are they What did
you do to my My Family!
Surely you see the seagulls around you.
I suppose we're finally approaching land.
And I finally have you
all to myself, Bucciarati.
You best!
Oh, aspetta, aspetta, aspetta!
Uh-uh-uh.
I'm the one who's talking here, not you.
Now keep that mouth shut till I tell
you otherwise, test any cats all!
That's it.
Know that I can eliminate
you at any moment.
Your little minions live
only because I allow it.
They're in a state of suspended animation.
You should be grateful they
aren't sleeping with the fishes.
I'd have to chop them into bite-sized
pieces for the little ones.
If you decide to cooperate, however,
I could return your crew to normal.
Of course,
you need to tell me where Polpo has been
hiding that wonderful treasure of his.
Tell me, are you part of Passione?
Gee whiz, you really just
aren't getting it, are you?
I'll kill you, Kanzone!
Listen up!
I only want to hear about
the location of the loot!
Try to shit out anything
else from that disgusting
bunghole slapped across your
face and see what happens!
If you so much as scrunch without permission,
one of your pals are getting offed!
Say nothing, and I'll kill them!
And if I find out you lied, they die!
Agapito, choose your
words extremely carefully.
Now,
to address the 10 billion
lira manatee on the boat,
where can I find the money
the boss left behind?
Black-tailed gulls.
Huh? Come again?
Those birds are black-tailed
gulls not seagulls.
If you're wondering how I can tell,
it's because they sound like
they're meowing you mentioned
before they were seagulls but
they're really black-tailed gulls.
Say goodbye to your comrade.
Just try it.
If hell doesn't drag you down first?
W-what the hell are you doing?!
I didn't strike the deck in order to
find out where you'd hidden Abakio.
I just wanted to create a little leak.
But why?!
Abakio unraveled the mystery
behind your special hiding spot.
and he was nice enough to
leave some evidence there.
Evidence of your location and even
of your distinguishing features.
He did it with his blood.
Abakyo went so far as to injure his own
hand so as to leave behind a trail of blood.
He was taken, but the blood
never seeped below the deck.
It stops right at the floorboard, which
I find more than a little curious.
There must be a reason.
Where were he and the others taken?
I rented the yacht that was on the left.
Abakio realized that when
he looked up at the sky.
Your cover's been blown.
If you don't want to drown to
death, I'd suggest coming out.
There were two boats all along.
You bastard!
You hid yourself by stretching one yacht
over another like some kind of a thin skin.
You moved within the slim space
created between the boats,
ambushing us as you pleased.
Quite the conundrum.
You have my deepest compliments.
I'd stay still if I were you, Butcherati!
Or do you want your comrades to die?!
You of all people should know
you wouldn't last one day as
a mafioso if a feeble threat
like that rattled your bones.
Give up and I'll show mercy.
But the moment you injure a Bakio,
I'm putting you down for good.
It's just like Jean said,
your need to remain hidden while
attacking is a point of weakness.
You need some speed.
Epakio...
Bravissimo.
I'm about nothing else.
Freaking you is all I need.
Tonight, I need your body!
I need your body!
Tonight, you got my time.
Tonight, you won't be sorry!
Tonight, you got my mind.
You got my mind, all I
wanna do is freak you.
What must I say, what must I do?
To show how much I'm gonna freak you.
To show how much I'm gonna freak you?
Abakion.
The end result isn't what matters most.
It's the moments along the way.
I want you to join us.
Don't live your life stuck in the past.
Thank you.
You